rsportscars.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - NameJet Domain Name Services

NameJet knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in connection with your use of our websites, platform, services and/or mobile applications (collectively and individually referred to herein as our "Services"). By visiting this or another NameJet website displaying this Privacy Policy or a link thereto (the "Website", or collectively the "Websites"), or by creating a NameJet account or otherwise using or accepting our Services, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We encourage you to read the entire Privacy Policy, and for any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact NameJet using our contact information found here or by submitting a ticket from your NameJet account. 

### What Information Is Collected

Contact Information.
     We collect and retain personal contact information that you submit to us voluntarily in signing up for our Services, mailing lists, or visiting our Websites. This includes your name, mailing address, web address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address. Additionally, we collect contact information provided to us during any correspondence relating to customer support, as well as in connection with the use of our Services. 
Financial Information and Account-Related Information.
     We collect and retain financial information you provide when you create a NameJet account or otherwise use our Services. For example, when you create a NameJet account, we require you to provide a credit card number and billing address before we activate that account. We also collect information related to your use of our Services, such as account number, purchases, backorders, bids and customer service requests and notes or details explaining what you asked for and how we responded. 
Cookies and Other Information Related to Use of the Website.
     We collect information about the device with which users access the Website and information related to their use of the Website itself, such as the domain name, Internet Service Provider, browser type and version, pages viewed, and information accessed. We may also gather general information such as the date, time, operating system, platform, navigation history, and IP address of users to our Website. We use this information for our internal security audit logs, trend analysis, and system administration, and to gather broad demographic information about our users. We may also associate this general information with your personal information. By visiting our Website, you affirmatively consent to our collection and use of this information in line with the foregoing. 

Additionally, our Website places cookies, which are small data files on the user's hard drive when they visit our Website. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser; however, if you reject the placement of cookies, you may be limited in using our Website and Services. Some cookies are used to improve your user experience by making logging into our Website easier, such as by remembering usernames and passwords. Cookies can also enable us to monitor users' movements through our Website so that we may target user interests to enhance their experience at our Website. We may also collect click stream data such as the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) and assign unique identifiers to our users for the purpose of tracking user behaviors. Information obtained with these technologies may be associated with the personal information you have provided us. Besides using the information as described above, NameJet may utilize cookies to control operations such as the flow of the ordering processes related to your online transactions. Additional information regarding our use of cookies can be found in our Cookies Policy located here.

We, or our third-party advertising partners, may also place cookies to provide advertisements about goods or services that may be of interest to you. Since our advertisers and other third parties whose products or services are promoted on our Website may also use cookies or other technology, we advise you to check the advertisers' privacy policies for information about their privacy practices. 

### How Information Is Used

NameJet believes in limiting the use of your personal information and only looks to collect or use it (a) where we have been given permission, (b) as necessary to provide the Services, or (c) as we may be required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes. These uses include: 

To Perform our Contract with You or Otherwise Provide our Services to You.
     We use this information to perform our contract with you and fulfil your Services requests, such as: 

  * Sending you requested service information;
  * Processing your backorders and bids;
  * Fulfilling your orders;
  * Billing for Services;
  * Responding to customer service requests, questions and concerns; and
  * Administering your account.

Note that, generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are transactional and not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to not utilize our Website and/or Services. 

We also engage other companies, individuals, and affiliates to perform certain functions and services for you on our behalf. These third parties: 

  * Process credit card payments;
  * Provide marketing assistance, including but not limited to email delivery services and email list management;
  * Analyze data; and
  * Provision domains names you purchase or otherwise win on NameJet, which may involve creation of an account by a partner registrar or otherwise delivering a domain name to your existing account with that registrar, at which point you shall become a customer of that registrar if you are not one already.

These parties have access to user information needed to perform their functions for the benefit of the user. These parties may, or may not, retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to NameJet for any secondary purposes. 

To Contact You

If you have given your consent to send you email, phone or SMS marketing, or if you have provided us with your postal address, we will use the personal data you give to us to contact you from time to time. If you create a NameJet account, you can select which marketing emails you receive by updating your Email Preferences as follows: 

If you want to change your Email Preferences, you may do so by following these steps: 

  1. 1\. Login to "My Account";
  2. 2\. Select the "Preferences" tab; and
  3. 3\. Choose your email settings under "Email Preferences"

If you do not want to receive electronic communications, you may withdraw your consent at any time, by changing your Email Preferences, clicking the unsubscribe link in an email communication, or emailing us using the address provided below. Note that, generally, you may not opt-out of communications that are transactional and not promotional in nature, or otherwise are for a legitimate business interest. If you do not wish to receive these types of notices, you have the option to not utilize our Website and/or Services. 

For services in the United States, by creating an account on NameJet and providing your telephone number, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or application for purposes of telemarketing laws. Regardless of the fact that your telephone and/or cell number may be listed with the Federal Do-Not-Call Registry or your local State Do-Not-Call list, you are providing your express written consent to receive future information (including telemarketing) about products and services from us and/or our affiliates, and you hereby agree and consent to our contacting you using the information you have provided and will provide to us. This means we may contact you by e-mail, phone and/or cell number (including use of automated dialing equipment and/or pre-recorded calls), text (SMS) message, social networks or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving (i.e. video, etc.). We may also send you information or offers from time to time to the postal address or email address we have on file (as further outlined in this Privacy Policy). 

To Protect our Website, Business and Customers.

We monitor use of the Websites and we use the information we collect, including personal data, to pursue our legitimate interest in protecting you, others, NameJet, its business and the Websites by: 

  * Identifying fraudulent activities and transactions;
  * Preventing abuse of the Websites and Services and investigating and/or seeking prosecution for any potential threats to or misuse of the Websites and Services;
  * Investigating violations of and ensuring compliance with our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy; and 
  * Protecting the rights and property of NameJet, its partners, and customers.

We further release account and other personal information when we believe release is required to comply with federal or state law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of NameJet, our users, or others. This includes potentially exchanging information with other companies, organizations and members of law enforcement to protect against fraud or other criminal or improper activity. 

To Improve Our Services.
     In order to pursue our legitimate interest in improving our Services and Websites, we also may use personal information to conduct research and analysis. We do this to (a) better understand how people interact with our Websites and use our Services, (b) make improvement to the Services and Websites, (c) identify domain name inventory of interest to customers, (d) identify what features would be useful to our customers, (e) provide communications about Services which we think will be of interest to our customers, and (f) further determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising. 
To Provide Required Information to ICANN.
     When you purchase or otherwise obtain a domain via NameJet, your domain purchase will be fulfilled by one of our partner registrars. These registrars are required by the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), the organization that assumes responsibility for domain name allocation, to collect and use your personal information during the domain name registration process. This information includes your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number. ICANN then requires all registrars to make your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the name server information associated with your domain name, to the public via an interactive Web page and a "port 43" WHOIS service. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy we will refer to this information as your "WHOIS Information." Each of our partner registrars may handle this responsibility differently, as some may choose to mask your personally identifiable information as they feel is necessary, including but not limited to, masking data published to Port 43 or the WHOIS database. Please be sure to review the Registrar Agreements and Privacy Policies for all our partner registrars, which you have agreed to via our Terms of Use, in order to be aware of how each partner registrar will handle and use your information. Also, please note that we do not control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information. 

### Information Security

The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, disclosure, or destruction of that information. We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate. Specifically, we often protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and the information we may send to our agents. NameJet has gone to great lengths to ensure your information is securely obtained. For example, we encrypt your credit card number before it is stored in our database. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is completely secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You can further help to ensure your security by taking a few simple precautions. For instance, it is important to protect against unauthorized access to your computer and your NameJet account username and password, and to be sure to sign off when you are finished using a shared computer. 

### Retention Policy

We retain personal information for as long as necessary to provide the Services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods that are (a) mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations; (b) needed for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal and/or contractual rights; or (c) necessary to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records. 

### Information Access

You have certain rights to your personal information, including but not limited to the following: 

  * To access a copy of your personal data;
  * To correct, erase or restrict our processing of your personal data;
  * To transfer the information you have provided under contract or consent to another organization; and
  * To stop processing your information, by withdrawing your consent or objecting to our legitimate interests.

Your rights in relation to your personal information are limited in some situations. For example, if we have a legal requirement or a compelling legitimate ground we may continue to process your information. We will provide you with clarification regarding whether there are limits or exemptions that apply to any data request that you make. To access, view, update or delete your available personal information, or to otherwise update your account preferences, please log into your account for such access and/or submit a ticket via the account. Please note, however, that no information will be provided without verification. Also, if you make a request to delete or change your personal information and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record-keeping obligations. 

You have the right to make a complaint if you feel your personal information has been mishandled. We encourage you to come to us in the first instance but, to the extent that this right applies to you, you are entitled to complain directly to the relevant supervisory authority. This can be the supervisory authority where you reside or work, or where you believe a breach has taken place. 

If you are unable for any reason to access your NameJet account please contact us via our contact information found here. 

### Links

The Websites provided by NameJet contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Website. 

### Age Restrictions & Children

You must be at least eighteen years old to register online or purchase or otherwise use our Services. If you are under 18, you may use our Services only with involvement of a parent or guardian. NameJet does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of eighteen. If you know of or have reason to believe anyone under the age of 18 has provided us with any personal data, please contact us. 

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit our Website, create a NameJet account, and/or utilize our Services, any dispute over privacy related to the same is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Commonwealth of Virginia. If you have any concern about privacy at NameJet, please send us your concern using our contact information found here or submit a ticket via your NameJet account, and we will investigate and address it as necessary. Our business changes constantly – so we reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, by email, and/or by means of a notice on our home page of our Website prior to the implementation of the changes. 

Also, as we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if NameJet, or substantially all of its assets, were ever to be acquired, customer information would most likely be one of the transferred assets. 

### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via the contact information found here, or submit a ticket via your NameJet account.
